This is the people's show.
[NOISE]
>> Speaker 2: And
you know what that means?
[NOISE]
[MUSIC]
>> Speaker 3: You know
whose ring you're in?
[NOISE]
>> It's
been a long time, Rock, a long time.
But let me go ahead and tell you-
>> Speaker 4: You shut your bitch ass up.
[NOISE]
>> Speaker 1: You clearly don't know how
all this works.
[NOISE]
>> Finally The Rock has come
back to Denver.
[NOISE]
>> Maybe I should try.
Finally, the ignorant people
get to see The Rock and
Austin back in the ring
again one last time.
Only this time,
it's not boring old Stone Cold.
It's a real Austin, a real ass kicker.
The Austin that is gonna go on and
be so great.
I'm gonna be the entire Mount Rushmore.
Yeah, that's how great.
>> Speaker 2: Well, The Rock says-
>> It doesn't matter what The Rock says.
>> [LAUGH]
[NOISE]
>> Speaker 1: You see,
it actually does matter
what The Rock says.
[NOISE]
>> And it
actually does matter more importantly than
what The Rock says, what the people say.
[NOISE]
>> You bring up Stone Cold Steve Austin.
That's The Rock's, boy.
But if he were here right now,
this is what he would say.
If you wanna see me beat this
gibroni's ass, give me a hell yeah.
>> Hell, yeah.
>> So you see the roof just brew
off the place because we are live.
And as The Rock said, this is The Rock.
It's SmackDown and it's The Rock's
show and it matters what they say.
So you see how loud they just got, right?
So you wanna talk trash about Stone Cold,
talk trash about Pat,
talk trash about the people.
Well, The Rock says this,
you're Austin Theory, right?
>> Speaker 1: You're damn right.
>> Speaker 6: Right, right, right,
and you're from A town, is that right?
>> Speaker 1: You're damn right.
>> Speaker 1: Well, something else that
I'm damn right about is you clearly
are an A-hole.
[NOISE]
>> And
I'm gonna show you, The Rock is
gonna show you, because we are live.
And here's how The Rock is gonna
show you you're such an A-hole.
You see, in about three seconds, this
side of the arena is gonna chant you are.
And then this side of
the arena is gonna chant.
[NOISE]
>> Speaker 1: Three, two, one.
>> Speaker 5: You are.
You are.
>> Speaker 3: So sorry,
hold on one second.
That was amazing, by the way,
Denver, Colorado.
[NOISE]
>> Speaker 6: That was amazing.
The Rock has got goosebumps right there.
But you know what?
This is The Rock show.
It's a people's show.
This is the people.
Now we're gonna give this side
a chance to say you are, and
this side a chance to say.
Three, two, one.
>> You are.
You are.
>> Speaker 7: Shut up your damn mouth,
be quiet.
Stop, I am not, no.
[NOISE]
>> Speaker 1: Two hours,
The Rock knows the show is two hours.
But right now, The Rock and
the people, we're having fun, baby.
[NOISE]
>> Here's a lesson for you.
The Rock doesn't know who you are,
but he knows what you are.
And clearly, you're a, but
let The Rock tell you this.
Let The Rock tell you this.
Your name is Austin Theory.
The Rock has a theory of his own,
and here's the thing.
You come out here on The Rock show,
the people's show, SmackDown.
You run down the people.
They're the reasons why
it makes it all happen.
The Rock says this.
Here's The Rock's theory.
In about three seconds, The Rock is gonna
whoop your candy ass all over Denver.
[NOISE]
>> Speaker 5: Theory went after The Rock.
>> Speaker 2: How brave, how bold.
>> How stupid may that be?
>> Speaker 2: And went for
the spine buster, and here it comes.
Here it comes.
>> Speaker 2: Get out of there, Theory.
>> Speaker 2: Are you ready?
[NOISE]
>> It's been a long time.
>> No, Theory's about to experience it,
the most electrifying move in all of
entertainment, the people's elbow.
[MUSIC]
>> Speaker 8: No, no, Rocky,
don't encourage this mouth breather.
>> Speaker 2: And
now McAfee with the opportunity.
[NOISE]
>> Can
you imagine being in the ring and having
The Rock instruct you to do his own move?
>> Speaker 8: Sit down, I don't think
it's healthy to be upright at your age.
>> Speaker 2: McAfee
gonna deliver it as well.
McAfee taking his time,
into a People's elbow.
[MUSIC]
What a star studded night.
>> Speaker 2: Are you kidding me?
>> Speaker 4: I can tell from
experience that people elbow hurts.
[MUSIC]
>> Speaker 3: What a start
to Friday Night SmackDown.